{
    "target_configs": {
        "player": {
            "name": [
                "player_16_SBE5Z4",
                "player_5_SBE5Z4",
                "player_12_SBE5Z4",
                "player_4_SBE5Z4",
                "player_3_SBE5Z4"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                16,
                5,
                12,
                4,
                3
            ],
            "animation": [
                "stand",
                "crouch",
                "pick_up",
                "stand",
                "crouch"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "A man with dark skin, wearing a black fedora, black turtleneck, black pants, and black shoes.",
                "A female soldier wearing green tactical uniform, backpack, and black boots. Hair is tied back. She carries a utility vest and accessories.",
                "A man wearing a gray suit, dark shirt, and brown shoes with short dark hair.",
                "A woman with fair skin, wearing a white and blue shirt, blue pants, dark boots, a gray bandana, and a utility belt with pouches",
                "A woman with medium skin, dark hair in a bun, wearing a dark V-neck shirt, light pants, and brown boots"
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    18595.292,
                    -81740.665,
                    5404.673,
                    0,
                    -139.08703782127833,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    18668.011,
                    -81871.358,
                    5391.787,
                    0,
                    44.51160572050031,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    18494.689,
                    -81879.06,
                    5386.548,
                    0.0,
                    -89.999,
                    0.0
                ],
                [
                    18915.19,
                    -81733.324,
                    5386.774,
                    0,
                    -30.247982738140053,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    18355.814,
                    -82453.546,
                    5319.78,
                    0,
                    156.51552891466235,
                    0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None"
            ]
        }
    },
    "sample_configs": {
        "sample_center": [
            18443.927,
            -82421.692,
            5285.352
        ],
        "sample_radius": 1040.3723821479393
    },
    "refer_agents_category": [
        "player"
    ],
    "safe_start": [
        [
            19329.708,
            -81469.112,
            5326.022,
            0,
            -147.21089873132019,
            0
        ],
        [
            19250.501,
            -82643.164,
            5222.909,
            0,
            132.33420053405285,
            0
        ],
        [
            17579.278,
            -82243.162,
            5296.081,
            0,
            16.68649968268454,
            0
        ]
    ],
    "Questions": {
        "relative_distance": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_fedora_hat, the_woman_in_camo_vest or the_woman_in_floral_shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_camo_vest",
                    "B. the_woman_in_floral_shirt"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_camo_vest"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_fedora_hat, the_man_in_grey_suit or the_woman_in_deep_V_top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_grey_suit",
                    "B. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_grey_suit"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_fedora_hat, the_woman_in_floral_shirt or the_woman_in_deep_V_top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_floral_shirt",
                    "B. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_floral_shirt"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_camo_vest, the_man_in_fedora_hat or the_woman_in_floral_shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_fedora_hat",
                    "B. the_woman_in_floral_shirt"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_fedora_hat"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_camo_vest, the_man_in_grey_suit or the_woman_in_deep_V_top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_grey_suit",
                    "B. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_grey_suit"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_grey_suit, the_man_in_fedora_hat or the_woman_in_floral_shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_fedora_hat",
                    "B. the_woman_in_floral_shirt"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_fedora_hat"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_grey_suit, the_woman_in_camo_vest or the_woman_in_deep_V_top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_camo_vest",
                    "B. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_camo_vest"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_floral_shirt, the_woman_in_camo_vest or the_woman_in_deep_V_top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_camo_vest",
                    "B. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_camo_vest"
            }
        },
        "counting": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "How many humans are in the scene?",
                "answer": "five"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "How many humans are in a standing position?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "How many humans are in a crouch position?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "How many humans are picking something up?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "How many men are in the scene?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "How many women are in the scene?",
                "answer": "three"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "How many humans in the scene have light skin color?",
                "answer": "three"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "How many humans in the scene have black skin color?",
                "answer": "one"
            }
        },
        "state": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "What is the state of the man wearing a fedora hat?",
                "options": [
                    "A. stand",
                    "B. crouch",
                    "C. holding an object",
                    "D. sitting"
                ],
                "answer": "A. stand"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "What is the state of the woman in the camo vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. stand",
                    "B. crouch",
                    "C. walking",
                    "D. holding an object"
                ],
                "answer": "B. crouch"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "What is the state of the man in the grey suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. sitting",
                    "B. crouching",
                    "C. holding an object",
                    "D. walking"
                ],
                "answer": "C. holding an object"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "What is the state of the woman in the floral shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. stand",
                    "B. crouch",
                    "C. pick_up",
                    "D. sitting"
                ],
                "answer": "A. stand"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "What is the state of the woman wearing a deep V-neck top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. stand",
                    "B. crouching",
                    "C. lying down",
                    "D. holding an object"
                ],
                "answer": "B. crouching"
            }
        },
        "relative_location": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in floral shirt relative to the man in fedora hat?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "A. To the front of"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Where is the man in grey suit relative to the woman in camo vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. Behind"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in deep V top relative to the man in grey suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "A. To the front of"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Where is the man in fedora hat relative to the woman in floral shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. Behind"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in camo vest relative to the man in grey suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "D. To the right of"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in floral shirt relative to the man in grey suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "D. To the right of"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Where is the man in fedora hat relative to the woman in deep V top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "D. To the right of"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Where is the man in grey suit relative to the woman in deep V top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "D. To the right of"
            }
        }
    }
}